Finding Aid for Law School (University of Michigan) publications 1859-2015
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Printed Materials
  - Alumni Publications
    - Class of, 1894
      - Newsletters
        - The Bulletin
          - Volumes 1-2, 1920-1939 (Box 15)
        - Nunc Pro Tunc, 1944 (Box 15)
    - Class of, 1895 (Box 16)
      - Directories, 1897-1940 (Box 16)
    - Class of, 1896
      - Directories, 1906-1947 (Box 16)
    - Class of, 1897
      - Newsletters
        - Class Bulletin, 1898-1962 (Box 16)
    - Class of, 1898
      - Directories, 1923; 1938 (Box 16)
    - Class of, 1900
      - Directories, 1906-1950 (Box 16)
      - Histories, 1943; 1946 (Box 16)
    - Class of, 1901
      - Directories, 1902-1931 (Box 16)
    - Class of, 1902
      - Directories, 1916-1952 (Box 16)
    - Class of, 1903
      - Directories, 1904-1905; undated (Box 16)
    - Class of, 1904
      - Directories, 1924 (Box 16)
    - Class of, 1906
      - Directories, 1917-1936 (Box 16)
    - Class of, 1908
      - Directories, 1929 (Box 16)
    - Class of, 1909
      - Directories, 1951 (Box 16)
    - Class of, 1913
      - Directories, 1939 (Box 16)
    - Class of, 1914
      - Directories, 1949 (Box 16)
      - Newsletters
        - The Senior Law Crease, undated (Box 16)
    - Class of, 1918
      - Histories
        - Class History, undated (Box 16)
    - Class of, 1922
      - Class Day Exercises, 1922 (Box 16)
      - Directories, 1939; 1962; 1967 (Box 16)
    - Class of, 1926
      - Directories, 1940 (Box 16)
    - Class of, 1928
      - Directories, 1948 (Box 16)
    - Class of, 1929
      - Directories, 1940 (Box 16)
    - Class of, 1933
      - Directories, 1935-1938 (Box 16)
    - Class of, 1942
      - Directories-Class Notes, 1997 (Box 16)
    - Class of, 1943-1945
      - Directories-Class Notes, 1994 (Box 16)
    - Class of, 1946/47
      - Directories-Class Notes, 1997 (Box 16)
    - Class of, 1948
      - Directories-Class Notes, 1993 (Box 16)
    - Class of, 1948
      - Directories
        - Roster, 1949 (Box 16)
    - Class of, 1949
      - Directories, 1959 (Box 16)
      - Twenty-Fifth Reunion, September, 1974 (Box 16)
      - Fiftieth Reunion, October 1-3, 1999 (Box 16)
    - Class of, 1950
      - Reunion, 2000 (Box 16)
    - Class of, 1952
      - Directories-Class Notes, 1992; 1997; 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Class of, 1953
      - Directories-Class Notes, 1993 (Box 16)
    - Class of, 1954
      - Directories-Class Notes, 1994 (Box 16)
      - Forty-Fifth Reunion, October 1-3, 1999 (Box 16)
    - Class of, 1955
      - Reunion, 2000 (Box 16)
    - Class of, 1956
      - Directories, 1981 (Box 16)
    - Class of, 1957
      - Directories
        - The Journal of L'57 35th Reunion, 1992 (Box 16)
        - L '57 Then-And-Now Yearbook, 1957-1987; 1987 (Box 16)
    - Class of, 1958
      - Directories-Class Notes, 1993 (Box 16)
    - Class of, 1959
      - Directories-Class Notes, 1994 (Box 16)
      - Fortieth Reunion, October 1-3, 1999 (Box 16)
    - Class of, 1960
      - Reunion, 2000 (Box 16)
    - Class of, 1962
      - Directories-Class Notes, 1992; 1997 (Box 16)
    - Class of, 1963
      - Directories-Class Notes, 1993 (Box 16)
    - Class of, 1964
      - Directories-Class Notes, 1994 (Box 16)
      - Thirty Fifth Reunion, October 1-3, 1999 (Box 16)
    - Class of, 1965
      - Reunion, 2000 (Box 16)
    - Class of, 1967
      - Directories-Class Notes, 1992; 1997; 2 folders (Box 16)
    - Class of, 1968 (Box 17)
      - Directories-Class Notes, 1993 (Box 17)
      - Twenty-Fifth Reunion Reunion Briefs, 1993 (Box 17)
    - Class of, 1969
      - Directories-Class Notes, 1994 (Box 17)
      - Thirtieth Reunion, October 1-3, 1999 (Box 17)
    - Class of, 1970
      - Reunion, 2000 (Box 17)
    - Class of, 1972
      - Directories-Class Notes, 1992; 1997; 2 folders (Box 17)
    - Class of, 1973
      - Directories-Class Notes, 1993 (Box 17)
    - Class of, 1974
      - Directories-Class Notes, 1994 (Box 17)
      - Twenty-Fifth Reunion, November 5-7, 1999 (Box 17)
    - Class of, 1975
      - Reunion, 2000 (Box 17)
    - Class of, 1977
      - Directories-Class Notes, 1992; 1997; 2 folders (Box 17)
    - Class of, 1978
      - Directories-Class Notes, 1993 (Box 17)
    - Class of, 1979
      - Directories
        - Class Notes, 1994 (Box 17)
        - Twentieth Reunion, November 5-7, 1999 (Box 17)
    - Class of, 1980
      - Reunion, 2000 (Box 17)
    - Class of, 1982
      - Directories-Class Notes, 1992; 1997; 2 folders (Box 17)
    - Class of, 1983
      - Directories-Class Notes, 1993 (Box 17)
    - Class of, 1984
      - Directories-Class Notes, 1994 (Box 17)
      - Fifteenth Reunion, November 5-7, 1999 (Box 17)
    - Class of, 1985
      - Directories-Class Notes, 1994 (Box 17)
      - Reunion, 2000 (Box 17)
    - Class of, 1987
      - Directories-Class Notes, 1992; 1997 (Box 17)
    - Class of, 1988
      - Directories-Class Notes, 1993 (Box 17)
    - Class of, 1989
      - Directories-Class Notes, 1994 (Box 17)
      - Tenth Reunion, November 5-7, 1999 (Box 17)
    - Class of, 1990
      - Directories -- Class Notes, 1995 (Box 17)
      - Reunion, 2000 (Box 17)
    - Class of, 1992
      - Directories-Class Notes, 1997 (Box 17)
    - Class of, 1994
      - Directories (Box 17)
      - Fifth Reunion, November 5-7, 1999 (Box 17)
    - Class of, 1995
      - Directories (Box 17)
      - Reunion, 2000 (Box 17)
    - International Alumni Reunion
      - Brochures, 1991 (Box 17)
      - Directories- Biography Book, 1991 (Box 17)
      - Programs, 1991; 1997 (Box 17)
    - Michigan Black Law Alumni Society
      - Agenda, 1977 (Box 17)
      - Brochures, 1977 (Box 17)
      - Directory, 1979 (Box 17)
      - Newsletter, 1976-1977 (Box 17)
    - Michigan Law Alumni Reunion (Box 18)
      - Brochures, 1980-1985 (Box 18)
    - Michigan Law School Club of Washington
      - Newsletters, 1992-1993 (Box 18)
    - Minority Alumni Weekend
      - Directory, 1992-1993 (Box 18)
      - Program, 1993 (Box 18)
  - Topical Publications
    Topical Publications include materials from the Centennial Celebration, Conference on Legal Education, Diversity, Examination Questions, Henry M. Campbell Competition, Law Quadrangle, Oliver Wendell Holmes Devise Lectures, Summer Institute, and the Summer Session.
    - Alene and Allen F. Smith Professor of Law
      - Program, 1983 (Box 18)
    - Capital Campaign
      - Brochures, circa 1976 (Box 18)
    - Centennial Celebration
      - Addresses
        - Frontiers in Law and Legal Education, 1961 (Box 18)
      - Bulletins
        - 100th Anniversary News Bulletin, 1959 (Box 18)
      - Programs, 1959 (Box 18)
      - Reports
        - Centennial Observance: Law School of the University of Michigan (in Michigan State Bar Journal), 1959 (Box 18)
    - Coalition to Support BAM
      - Flyer, undated (Box 18)
      - Reports, undated (Box 18)
    - Conference on Aims and Methods of Legal Research
      - Programs, 1955 (Box 18)
    - Conference on Legal Education
      - Programs, 1959 (Box 18)
      - Reports
        - The Law Schools Look Ahead, 1959 (Box 18)
    - Diversity @ Michigan, 2006-2011 (Box 18)
    - Examination Questions
      - 1886-1934/35, 36 folders (Box 18)
      - 1935/36-1964/65, 15 folders (Box 19)
      - 1965/66-1978/79, undated; 8 folders (Box 20)
      - 100 Years of International Law Exams, undated (Box 20)
      - Second Year Examination Questions, 1903 (Box 20)
      - Third Year Examination Questions, 1903 (Box 20)
    - The George M. Humphrey Program in Law and Economic Policy
      - Lecture, 1968 (Box 20)
      - Poster, 1968 (Box 20)
      - Program, 1968 (Box 20)
    - The Henry M. Campbell Competition
      - Programs, 1977-1996 (Box 20)
    - Inter-American Bar Association University of Michigan Day
      - Programs, 1949 (Box 20)
    - The James E. and Sarah A. Degan Professor of Law
      - Program, 1982 (Box 20)
    - Law and Development Society
      - Program, 1996 (Box 20)
    - Law Quadrangle
      - Brochures
        - Guide to the Law Quadrangle, undated (Box 20)
      - Monographs
        - A Book of the Law Quadrangle at the University of Michigan, 1934 (Box 20)
      - Proceedings
        - Dedicatory Exercises of the Law Quadrangle, 1934 (Box 20)
      - Programs
        - Program for the Exercises and Dedication of the Law Quadrangle, 1934 (Box 20)
      - Reports
        - The Law Quadrangle at the University of Michigan, 1932 (Box 20)
    - Law School Institute
      - Postcards, 1953 (Box 21)
      - Programs, 1952 (Box 21)
    - Martin Luther King, Jr. Day
      - Flyer, 1991 (Box 21)
      - Programs, 1992-1995 (Box 21)
    - Michigan Law Revision Commission
      - 4th Annual Report, 1969 (Box 21)
    - Michigan Telecommunications and Technology Law Review
      - Programs, 2003-2006 (Box 21)
    - Midwest Regional Conference on Women and the Law
      - Brochure, 1979 (Box 21)
    - Minority Affairs Summer Program
      - Brochures, undated (Box 21)
      - Handbooks, 1991-1995; 5 folders (Box 21)
    - Minority Students' Pre-Law Conference Report, 1971 (Box 21)
    - New Academic Building and Law School Commons, 2009 (Box 21)
    - Oil and Gas Law Institute
      - Programs, 1949 (Box 21)
    - Oliver Wendall Holmes Devise Lectures, 1971 (Box 21)
    - Reading Room Concert
      - Programs, 1987-1994 (Box 21)
    - Robert A. Sullivan Professor of Law
      - Program, 1984 (Box 21)
    - Sesquicentennial, 2009 (Box 21)
    - Staff Brown Bag
      - Flyers, undated (Box 21)
    - Summer Institute
      - Programs, 1949-1958 (Box 21)
    - The Summer Institute on International and Comparative Law
      - Lectures
        - Communications Media Legal and Policy Problems, 1954 (Box 21)
        - The Conflict of Laws and International Contracts, 1949 (Box 21)
        - International Law and the United Nations, 1955 (Box 21)
        - Taxation of Business Enterprise, 1951 (Box 21)
    - The Thomas E. Sunderland Faculty Fellowships
      - Brochures, undated (Box 21)
    - Walking Tours
      - Self-Guided Tour, undated (Box 21)
      - Self-Guided Walking Tour, undated (Box 21)
      - Walking Tour, undated (Box 21)
  - Student Publications
    Student Publications are divided into two subseries: General and Individual. General publications include an anthology of student writing and the newsletter Res Gestae. Individual publications include materials produced by the Ad-Hoc Committee on Issues of Race, Gender, and Sexual Orientation which produced the newsletter Res Ipsa Loquitur, the American Indian Law Students Association, the Christiancy Senate no. 1, the Barristers Society, which produced the Michigan Raw Review, the Black Law Students Alliance, the Hispanic Law Students Alliance, La Raza Law Students' Association, the Law Student Association, the Student Bar Association, the Webster Society and the Women Law Students Association.
    - General
      - Anthologies
        - Selections to Remember from a Year to Forget, undated (Box 21)
      - Newsletters
        - Res Gestae, 1950-1951; 1953-1954; 1957; 1960; 1962-1969; 12 folders (Box 21)
        - Res Gestae, 1969-1983/84; 5 folders (Box 22)
        - Res Gestae, 1985/86-2004/05; 22 folders (Box 23)
        - Res Gestae, 2005/06-2010/11; 7 folders (Box 24)
        - Res Gestae, 2011/12- (Box 24)
        - Res Gestae, Archived Website
          The Res Gestae website includes recent editions of the online publication and is intended to eventually include pdf versions of the entire run of the newsletter.
    - Individual
      - Ad Hoc Committee on Issues of Race, Gender, and Sexual Orientation
        - Newsletters
          - Res Ipsa Loquitur (Box 24)
      - American Bar Association Law Student Division
        - Flyers, undated (Box 24)
      - American Indian Law Students Association
        - Brochures, undated (Box 24)
        - Programs
          - The Native American Environment: Land, Law & Controversy, undated (Box 24)
      - Asian Pacific American Law Student Association
        - Programs
          - Asian Pacific Americans and the Law, 1998 (Box 24)
      - Christiancy Senate no. 1
        - Newsletters
          - The Padded Hammer, undated (Box 24)
      - Barristers Society
        - Journals
          - Michigan Raw Review, 1936-1987; 5 folders (Box 24)
        - Programs
          - Initiation Banquet, 1932 (Box 24)
      - Black Law Students Alliance
        - Directories
          - Directory of Black Alumni 1885-1973, 1974 (Box 24)
        - Guides
          - A Guide to Getting Accepted to Law School, 1992 (Box 24)
        - Newsletters
          - BLSA Connection, 1976 (Box 24)
        - Programs
          - The Evolution of Malcolm X: The Man and the Myth, 1992 (Box 24)
          - Symposium on Employment Opportunities for Black Attorneys, 1972 (Box 24)
      - Griot: Literary and Arts Journal of the University of Michigan Law School, 2006 (Box 24)
      - Hispanic Law Students Association
        - Brochures, undated (Box 24)
      - Irish-American Law Student's Association
        - Brochures, undated (Box 24)
      - La Raza Las Students' Association
        - Brochures, undated (Box 24)
      - Latino Law Student Association
        - Brochures, 1996 (Box 24)
      - Law School Arts Association
        - Anthology Lawyers by Day, 1991-1992 (Box 24)
      - Law Students Against the War
        - Pamphlets, undated (Box 24)
      - Social Committee
        - Events Calendar, 1973 (Box 24)
      - Student Bar Association
        - Invitations, undated (Box 24)
        - Newsletters
          - Legal iggle, undated (Box 24)
        - Programs, undated (Box 24)
      - Webster Society
        - Constitution and By-Laws, 1905 (Box 24)
        - Programs
          - Public Exercises, 1874-1878 (Box 24)
      - Women Law Students Association
        - Brochures, undated (Box 24)
        - Newsletters
          - Newsletter, 1976-1977 (Box 24)
          - WLS Newsletter, 1975 (Box 24)
- Archived Law School Website
  The Archived Website series documents the academic programs, accomplishments, resources, events, and people at the Law School. Content includes important news and announcements, publications (such as newsletters and course catalogs), and information about admissions, curriculum, degree requirements, faculty, and the overall mission of the School. The website series is arranged chronologically, with captures from 2002 and 2003 stored on CD. Starting in 2010, this archived website will be captured on a regular, ongoing basis as part of the University of Michigan Web Archives, hosted at http://webarchives.cdlib.org/a/universityofmichigan/.
  - Website capture, May 15, 2002; 1 optical disks CDs (Box 2)
  - Website capture, June 22, 2003; 1 optical disks CDs (Box 3)
  - Archived Law School home page, 2010-[ongoing]
  - Archived websites related to the Law School, 2010-[ongoing]